{
    "subject": "resource/Unbelievable_Adventures_of_Italians_in_Russia",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributor",
    "object": "resource/Mosfilm",
    "human_readable": "The distributor of Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia is Mosfilm.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9792088270187378,
            "question": "Who distributes the film 'Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9649670124053955,
            "question": "Does 'Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia' have a distributor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.93323814868927,
            "question": "What is the name of the distributor for 'Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8942947387695312,
            "question": "What company handles the distribution of 'Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.73539137840271,
            "question": "Which film is distributed by Mosfilm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6938292384147644,
            "question": "Is Mosfilm involved in distributing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6842164993286133,
            "question": "Who is responsible for getting 'Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia' to viewers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5318899154663086,
            "question": "Mosfilm distributes what kind of content?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5046842098236084,
            "question": "What type of company is Mosfilm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48781391978263855,
            "question": "Can you name a film distributed by Mosfilm?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The distributor of Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia is Mosfilm.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5968_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Mosfilm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5968_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mosfilm distributes what kind of content?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5968_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is responsible for getting 'Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia' to viewers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5968_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5968_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe text states the film was a co-production of Mosfilm Studios and Dino de Laurentiis Cinematografica. It doesn't say Mosfilm was the sole distributor.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: In the context provided, there is a mention of \"Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia\" and it mentions that this film had a co-production with \"Mosfilm Studios\". Although it doesn't explicitly state Mosfilm as the distributor, given the context of co-productions often involving distributors, this can reasonably be inferred."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states that the distributor of \"Unbelievable Adventures of Italians in Russia\" is Mosfilm, but the provided text explicitly mentions a co-production between Mosfilm Studios and Dino de Laurentiis Cinematografica. This suggests that multiple distributors were involved, not just Mosfilm.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}